

Personal information

io.flrou@gmail.com



0766485306 70 Avenue d'Haifa



25 years old

Marseille

Skills

Google Ads

Google Analytics

Microsoft Office/Excel/Powerpoint

Facebook Ads

Language

Greek - Native

French - C1, Fluent

English - IELTS, Fluent

Links



Io FLOROU

Digital Marketing Consultant

Summary

Motivated Digital Marketing Consultant with strong background in Communication studies. I am currently an MSc student in Digital Marketing and Sales at Kedge Business School located in Marseille, France. I previously worked as a Google Ads Account Consultant of Greece, Cyprus and Malta in Teleperformance as part of a project with Google. I hold a BA in Communication and Media Studies from University of Athens, and I was also an Exchange Student in University of Porto.

Work Experience

Google Ads Account Consultant for Advertising Agencies in Greece, 10/2019 - 09/2020Cyprus & Malta / CDI

Teleperformance, Barcelona

- Enhanced 300 Google Ads Accounts of 50 different Agencies
- Managed portfolios of more than 1.2M of revenue each quarter
- Implemented creative ways to improve Agency relationships, tailor and share performance-enhancing suggestions for their end client accounts.
- Provided strategic advice and help agencies get the best ROI on their clients advertising investment by working closely with them in a consultative role.
- Developed creative ideas (Search, Display Network & YouTube).
- Consistently deliver against assigned quota, while prioritizing and delivering outstanding customer sales experience to Media Agencies.
- Deliver training sessions to colleagues on Google Ads to drive more sales.

Business Developer & Account Manager for the Greek Market / CDD Click&Boat, Paris 10/2018 - 10/2019

- Prospected more than **400 boats** for the platform
- Ad creation for boats, implementing the best SEO practices
- Worked as a member of the international Business Development
- Participation in the upgrade of the services, based on customer feedback
- Generated business with the Greek charter companies
- Management of more difficult and complex cases with the biggest charter companies

Education

MSc Digital Marketing & Sales

10/2020 - Present

Kedge Business School, France

BA in Communication & Media Studies

10/2013 - 06/2018

University of Athens

GPA: 7.4

• Specialization: Marketing Funnels & Communication

ERASMUS+ Student Exchange

01/2017 - 07/2017

University of Porto

Journalism & Communication



Piano, European filmography, Surfing, Volleyball